Panzo Editor Workbench smoke
  Scrub request-to-Present samples: 0
  Scrub request-to-Present P50/P95/P99/max us: 0/0/0/0
  Scrub source time error P95 tick: 0
  Scrub minimum distinct updates per 2 seconds: None
  Window created: true
  Output: 1920x1080
  Timer ticks: 45
  Rendered frames: 46
  Paint calls: 44
  Average render: 2165 us
  Maximum render: 52919 us
  Scripted OS input interruptions: 0
  Playback cadence samples: 43
  Playback Present P95: 18491 us
  Playback Present P99: 22456 us
  Playback Present maximum: 22456 us
  Background decodes: 0
  Source texture uploads: 45
  Background texture uploads: 0
  Output texture allocations: 0
  GPU direct preview: true
  GPU presentations: 46
  CPU readbacks: 0
  Last project tick: 7340303
  Graceful close: true
  Trim action elapsed: 0 us
  Trim smoke status: not-requested
  Queued playback completed: false
  Queued playback latency: 0 us
  Scrub presented frames: 0
  Scrub maximum presentation gap: 0 us
  Scrub release settled exactly: false
  Scrub distinct source frames: 0
  Scrub reduced-resolution frames: 0
  Scrub maximum source time error tick: 0
  Media errors: 0
